<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quoting Words</string>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>The most important thing is to enjoy your life – to be happy – it’s all that matters.\n\nAudrey Hepburn</item>
        <item>Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced.\n\nSoren Kierkegaard</item>
        <item>Very little is needed to make a happy life; it is all within yourself, in your way of thinking.\n\nMarcus Aurelius</item>
        <item>In the end, it’s not the years in your life that count. It’s the life in your years.\n\nAbraham Lincoln</item>
        <item>We do not remember days, we remember moments.\n\nCesare Pavese</item>
        <item>I have found that if you love life, life will love you back.\n\nArthur Rubinstein</item>
        <item>One way to get the most out of life is to look upon it as an adventure.\n\nWilliam Feather</item>
        <item>Life is a mirror and will reflect back to the thinker what he thinks into it.\n\nErnest Holmes</item>
        <item>If you love life, don’t waste time, for time is what life is made up of.\n\nBruce Lee</item>
        <item>It’s all about quality of life and finding a happy balance between work and friends and family.\n\nPhilip Green</item>
        <item>The greatest trap in our life is not success, popularity or power, but self-rejection.\n\nHenri Nouwen</item>
        <item>Life is ten percent what happens to you and ninety percent how you respond to it.\n\nLou Holtz</item>
        <item>The chief danger in life is that you may take too many precautions.\n\nAlfred Adler</item>
        <item>Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to reform (or pause and reflect).\n\nMark Twain</item>
        <item>The saddest aspect of life right now is that science gathers knowledge faster than society gathers wisdom.\n\nIsaac Asimov</item>
        <item>Any fool can know. The point is to understand.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>The simple things are also the most extraordinary things, and only the wise can see them.\n\nPaulo Coelho</item>
        <item>The man of knowledge must be able not only to love his enemies but also to hate his friends.\n\nFriedrich Nietzsche</item>
        <item>Follow your heart, listen to your inner voice, stop caring about what others think.\n\nRoy T. Bennett</item>
        <item>The measure of intelligence is the ability to change.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>It is not that I\'m so smart. But I stay with the questions much longer.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>Don\'t waste your time with explanations: people only hear what they want to hear.\n\nPaulo Coelho</item>
        <item>The past has no power over the present moment.\n\nEckhart Tolle</item>
        <item>Failure is the condiment that gives success its flavor.\n\nTruman Capote</item>
        <item>We can know only that we know nothing. And that is the highest degree of human wisdom.\n\nLeo Tolstoy</item>
        <item>The more I read, the more I acquire, the more certain I am that I know nothing.\n\nVoltaire</item>
        <item>Half of seeming clever is keeping your mouth shut at the right times.\n\nPatrick Rothfuss</item>
        <item>Life would be tragic if it weren\'t funny.\n\nStephen Hawking</item>
        <item>Risks must be taken because the greatest hazard in life is to risk nothing.\n\nLeo F. Buscaglia</item>
        <item>A day without sunshine is like, you know, night.\n\nSteve Martin</item>
        <item>Whenever I feel the need to exercise, I lie down until it goes away.\n\nPaul Terry</item>
        <item>It’s no use going back to yesterday, because I was a different person then.\n\nLewis Carroll</item>
        <item>Creativity is knowing how to hide your sources\n\nC.E.M. Joad</item>
        <item>Never memorize something that you can look up.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>If at first you don\'t succeed, try, try again. Then quit. No use being a damn fool about it.\n\nW.C. Fields</item>
        <item>The only man who never makes mistakes is the man who never does anything.\n\nTheodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>I have not failed. I\'ve just found 10,000 ways that won\'t work.\n\nThomas A. Edison</item>
        <item>It is never too late to be what you might have been.\n\nGeorge Eliot</item>
        <item>Life isn\'t about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself.\n\nGeorge Bernard Shaw</item>
        <item>Do what you can, with what you have, where you are.\n\nTheodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Do what you feel in your heart to be right – for you’ll be criticized anyway.\n\nEleanor Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Don\'t be pushed around by the fears in your mind. Be led by the dreams in your heart.\n\nRoy T. Bennett</item>
        <item>Life is too short to waste your time on people who don’t respect, appreciate, and value you.\n\nRoy T. Bennett</item>
        <item>You cannot control the behavior of others, but you can always choose how you respond to it.\n\nRoy T. Bennett</item>
        <item>Don\'t judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.\n\nRobert Louis Stevenson </item>
        <item>Without deviation from the norm, progress is not possible.\n\nFrank Zappa</item>
        <item>Trust yourself. You know more than you think you do.\n\nBenjamin Spock</item>
        <item>Do not fear to be eccentric in opinion, for every opinion now accepted was once eccentric.\n\nBertrand Russell</item>
        <item>It is better to fail in originality than to succeed in imitation.\n\nHerman Melville</item>
        <item>Have no fear of perfection - you\'ll never reach it.\n\nSalvador Dali</item>
        <item>The worst part of success is trying to find someone who is happy for you.\n\nBette Midler</item>
        <item>Sometimes it takes a good fall to really know where you stand\n\nHayley Williams</item>
        <item>It is hard to fail, but it is worse never to have tried to succeed.\n\nTheodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>The most courageous act is still to think for yourself. Aloud.\n\nCoco Chanel</item>
        <item>Insanity: doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>The greatest wealth is to live content with little.\n\nPlato</item>
        <item>The future belongs to those who prepare for it today.\n\nMalcolm X</item>
        <item>Those who dare to fail miserably can achieve greatly.\n\nJohn F. Kennedy</item>
        <item>In order to be irreplaceable one must always be different.\n\nCoco Chanel</item>
        <item>I like criticism. It makes you strong.\n\nLeBron James</item>
        <item>Well done is better than well said.\n\nBenjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.\n\nOscar Wilde</item>
        <item>The best things in life are free. The second best things are very expensive.\n\nCoco Chanel</item>
        <item>It’s not whether you get knocked down, it’s whether you get up.\n\nVince Lombardi</item>
        <item>Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world.\n\nNelson Mandela</item>
        <item>The only thing that interferes with my learning is my education.\n\nAlbert Einstein</item>
        <item>It always seems impossible until it’s done.\n\nNelson Mandela</item>
        <item>Life is a flower of which love is the honey.\n\nVictor Hugo</item>
        <item>It’s not how much you have that makes people look up to you, it’s who you are.\n\nElvis Presley</item>
        <item>A man who stands for nothing will fall for anything.\n\nMalcolm X</item>
        <item>You have power over your mind – not outside events. Realize this, and you will find strength.\n\nMarcus Aurelius</item>
        <item>The path to success is to take massive, determined action.\n\nTony Robbins</item>
        <item>Better to build a bridge than a wall.\n\nElton John</item>
        <item>Winners never quit, and quitters never win.\n\nVince Lombardi</item>
        <item>Doing the best at this moment puts you in the best place for the next moment.\n\nOprah Winfrey</item>
        <item>You never really learn much from hearing yourself speak.\n\nGeorge Clooney</item>
        <item>Someone’s sitting in the shade today because someone planted a tree a long time ago.\n\nWarren Buffett</item>
        <item>Doubt is not a pleasant condition, but certainty is absurd.\n\nVoltaire</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
